astatalk.com 2013-08-05

# Astatalk - Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes how Astatalk.com treat personal information when you use our services.

**Personal Information**

For some activities on Astatalk.com, such as submitting content (collectively referred to as "Submissions”), you need an Astatalk.com account. We ask for some personal information when you create an account, including your email address and a password, which is used to protect your account from unauthorised access.

**Usage Information**

When you use Astatalk.com, we may record information about your usage of the site. If you are logged in, we may associate that information with your Astatalk.com account.

Some information about your Astatalk.com account will be provided to other users of Astatalk.com.

**Submissions**

Any personal information that you voluntarily disclose online (e.g. your profile page) may be collected and used by others.

If you submit personal information to Astatalk.com, we may use that information to operate, maintain and improve the features and functionality of Astatalk.com.

We do not use your email address or other personal information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent.

We may use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes.

We use cookies to store information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time that you visit Astatalk.com and to provide custom, personalised content and information.

You may also choose to add personal information which may include your name, gender or other details, that will be visible to other users on your Astatalk.com account page.

If you have an Astatalk.com account, you may update or correct your personal profile information at any time by visiting your account profile page.

**More Information**

For questions concerning your account and our privacy practices, send us an email.
